import 'quiz_question_model.dart';

List<QuizQuestionModel> flutterQuestions = [
  QuizQuestionModel(
    question: "Flutter is written in what language?",
    options: ["Dart", "Python", "HTML", "CSS"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  ),
  QuizQuestionModel(
    question: "What color is the Flutter Logo?",
    options: ["Green", "Orange", "Blue", "Purple"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  ),
  QuizQuestionModel(
    question: "Which company created Flutter?",
    options: ["Google", "Tesla", "KFC", "Meta"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  ),
  QuizQuestionModel(
    question: "Which one is odd?",
    options: ["Container", "Row", "Column", "Elon Musk"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
  ),
  QuizQuestionModel(
    question: "Which doesn't belong here",
    options: ["Android", "IOS", "Windows", "Washing Machine"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
  ),
];

List<QuizQuestionModel> htmlQuestions = [
  QuizQuestionModel(
    question: "Tags contains except?",
    options: ["Open", "Close", "End", "Provider"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
  ),
  QuizQuestionModel(
    question: "How many types of headings are in html",
    options: ["6", "4", "12", "9"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  ),
  QuizQuestionModel(
    question: "HyperLinks could be in ways except?",
    options: ["Unvisited", "Listener", "Active", "Visited"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
  ),
  QuizQuestionModel(
    question: "Which tag is not used in a table",
    options: ["table", "tr", "Widget", "th"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  ),
  QuizQuestionModel(
    question: "Which list is commonly used in designing a page",
    options: ["Ordered", "FastList", "Round List", "For Loop"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  ),
];
